<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tutorials>

	<tutorial id="0" delay="0.5">
		
		<keyboard>Use the ARROW KEYS to move around and the SPACEBAR to attack or interact.</keyboard>
		<touch>Use the on-screen D-PAD to move around and the on-screen ACTION button to attack or interact.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>

	<tutorial id="1">
		
		<keyboard>When standing next to other characters, press SPACEBAR to interact.</keyboard>
		<touch>When standing next to other characters, tap the on-screen ACTION button to interact.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="2">
		
		<keyboard>Characters you meet and items you collect are recorded in SpongeBob's brain./Click on the BRAIN BUTTON at the top of the screen to access it.</keyboard>
		<touch>Characters you meet and items you collect are recorded in SpongeBob's brain./Tap on the BRAIN BUTTON at the top of the screen to access it.</touch>
		<image x="718" y="5">tutorial_circle</image>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="3" delay="0.5">
		
		<keyboard>To see exactly where you are within the current location, click on the MAP BUTTON.</keyboard>
		<touch>To see exactly where you are within the current location, tap on the MAP BUTTON.</touch>
		<image x="603" y="5">tutorial_circle</image>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="4">
		
		<keyboard>You can cycle through your equipment by clicking the icon in the top-left of the screen.</keyboard>
		<touch>You can cycle through your equipment by tapping the icon in the top-left of the screen.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="5">
		
		<keyboard>You can open clams and treasure chests by pressing the SPACEBAR while next to them.</keyboard>
		<touch>You can open clams and treasure chests by tapping the ACTION BUTTON while next to them.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="6">
		
		<keyboard>Use switches to open gates. Activate them by pressing the SPACEBAR.</keyboard>
		<touch>Use switches to open gates. Activate them by tapping the ACTION BUTTON.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>
	
	<tutorial id="7">
		
		<keyboard>Move through doors to new locations./Press SPACEBAR when standing next to a big yellow arrow.</keyboard>
		<touch>Move through doors to new locations./Tap the ACTION BUTTON when standing next to a big yellow arrow.</touch>
	
	</tutorial>
	
</tutorials>